welcome to Vitality I'm Dr Andy Galpin
I'm a professor in scientist with a PhD
in human bioenergetics standing next to
me is world-renowned human performance
specialist Dan Garner collectively we spent
nearly the last 20 years dedicated to the
science of humor performance we've got over a 100
peer-review Publications both spoken at National
and international conferences and worked with
professional athletes across over 15 different
Sports the way in which we've achieved Elite level
results across so many different disciplines lies
in removing the constraints of your physiology
here's the thing blood work gives a beautiful
representation in an objective way of what's
currently holding you back from being the best
possible version of yourself we've worked with
men women people interested in speed strength
fat loss mindset you name it it all comes back to
removing the constraint in your physiology that we
can identify in blood work and extrapolate into a
real world program to get real world results our
approach is a method we call the three eyes the
first stands for investigate which is what do I
measure and how do I get that done the second
is interpret how do I know if I'm good bad
great terrible or the best in world history
and the third is intervene which is what do
I specifically do about it to correct the problem
and maximize my result so if you couldn't tell Dan
and I are extremely passionate about leveraging
the science and Elite performers to help everyone
regardless of their goal look feel and perform
at their absolute best and with that we are
absolutely thrilled to bring to you the world's
first performance blood work platform to help
you investigate interpret and intervene so that
you can build a performance plan built for your
[Music]
physiology